LAVENDA ACHIENG

ENGLISH TEACHER



D.O.B: 20th Jan 1994

PROFILE -

CELTA qualified teacher with 2+ years' experience teaching children, adults and exam preparation. I enjoy utilizing my own activities in the classroom to help enhance the concepts we've learned in textbooks. I've been speaking English since I was a child.

CONTACT —

- Jiménez de la Espada 9, Cartagena 30204 Murcia, Spain
- +34 623 22 67 94
- teacherlavenda@outlook.com
- https://teacherlavenda.github.io
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/teacherlavenda

TEACHING EXPERIENCE -

JAN 2023 - PRESENT

Nursery Teacher Nice Day School Cartagena, Spain

- Teaching ages from 0 to 3
- Attending to children's basic needs
- Teach children in a safe and positive environment
- Monitoring and assessing children's progress
- Develop and produce visual aids and teaching resources
- Aid the development of a child's personal, social, language and physical coordination abilities

SEPT 2020 - DEC 2022

Private English Teacher Freelance Cartagena, Spain

- Teaching ages from 4 to adults
- Face to face classes and online classes
- Conversation and Trinity ISE exam preparation
- Use a variety of materials and resources
- Successfully taught each student to pass intermediate levels within 5 months
- Younger students were able to communicate in basic English after 3 months

OTHER EXPERIENCE

SEPT 2016 - FEB 2017

Social Worker Migori District Hospital Migori, Kenya

- Provision of counselling, advice and support to individuals
- Help children, elderly and families to solve their problems
- First aid provision
- Risk management
- Recognising the signs of child abuse

EDUCATION

DEC 2022

Oxford TEFL Barcelona, Spain

Workshops

- Teaching Business English
- Teaching Cambridge Exam Classes
- Teaching Young Learners

SEPT 2022

Oxford TEFL Barcelona, Spain

CELTA Course

- Work with elementary & upper intermediate students
- Taught more than 9 classes during the course

DEC 2020 - JUNE 2022

Instituto Cervantes Cartagena, Spain

Spanish Dele B2 Diploma Spanish Dele B1 Diploma

JUNE 2016

Sacred Heart Computer College Nairobi, Kenya

Certificate in computer packages

JAN 2013 - MAY 2016

Thika School of Medical and Health Sciences Nairobi, Kenya Diploma in Community Health and Development

Credit

Diploma in "Técnico Superior en Integración Social"

PERSONAL DEVELOPMENT -

JUNE 2018 - DEC 2019

AU-PAIR Cartagena, Spain Belluno, Italy

- Mentoring a young person
- Ensuring confidentiality
- Ensuring the welfare of Children
- Training in child protection responsibilities

- LANGUAGES -

COMPUTER SKILLS

Multilingual English Multilingual Swahili Multilingual Luo Advance Level Spanish Intermediate Level German Sufficient in using Microsoft Office, Google Docs, Skype, Zoom, Google Drive and One Drive

- Hobbies —

MOBILITY

REFERENCES —

Travelling, culture, reading and socializing

Full clean Spain driving license

Anna Stubs, Course Director, Oxford TEFL, Barcelona coursedirector@oxfordtefl.com
Nice Day School Cartagena gerencia@nicedayschool.es